Finding Aid for Vice-President for Development (University of Michigan) records, 1948-[ongoing]
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Development Office, 1943-1992
  - Staff Files
    - Topical File, 1979-1992
      - Development Office staff files
        - Proposal for Development Office staff expansion, 1976 (Box 32)
        - Staff meeting, 1977 (Box 32)
      - Development Relations Committees of the University of Michigan Alumni Association, 1983 (Box 32)
      - Donor clubs--miscellaneous, 1981-1984 (Box 32)
      - Donor recognition
        - Gender bias in, 1982-1984
          - Honor Roll, 1981/82-1983/84 (Box 32)
      - Donor records--access, 1982/83 (Box 32)
      - Endowments and investments, 1974-1982 (Box 32)
      - Financial aid to students, 1981 (Box 32)
      - First-time donors, 1981-1985 (Box 32)
      - Gerstacker Foundation, 1982-1983 (Box 32)
      - Gift income distribution, undated (Box 32)
      - Gift Receiving Office policies (Box 32)
      - Guidelines
        - Raffles, 1982 (Box 32)
        - Special donor groups (Box 32)
        - Premiums, 1980 (Box 32)
      - Hewlett Foundation Proposal, 1977 (Box 32)
      - Investment Programs, 1978; 1982/83 (Box 32)
      - International Alumni Program proposal, undated (Box 32)
      - Investment programs, 1978; 1982/83 (Box 32)
      - Lyons, Wendell R., recognition, 1982 (Box 32)
      - Major Gifts Program, A Proposal for the Improvement of, 1979 (Box 32)
      - Miller, Jim, 1972 (Box 32)
      - Organization and functions of University Relations and Development, ca., 1977 (Box 32)
      - Organization charts (Development Office), 1971-1990 (Box 32)
      - Parkes, David G., 1968-1969 (Box 32)
      - Personnel, 1982-1984 (Box 32)
      - Professorships at the University of Michigan, 1985 (Box 32)
        [holders of titled professorships]
      - School and College Relations: program analysis, 1981 (Box 32)
      - Student and faculty funding requests--policy, 1982 (Box 32)
      - Voluntary support for higher education, 1973-1974; 1977-1978 (Box 32)
      - Miscellaneous, 1976; 1980-1984 (Box 32)
  - Capital Campaigns, 1964-1994
    - $55 Million Campaign, 1964-1970
      - An Analysis of Donors of $10,000 or More to the $55 Million Program at the University of Michigan, Dissertation of Donald Morris, 1970 (Box 43)
      - Brochure Preserving the Michigan Story: A Building or the Michigan Historical Collections... (Box 43)
      - Campaign Briefs, November 1964-November 1967 (Box 43)
      - Gift opportunities/ financial objectives, 1965-1966 (Box 43)
      - Pattern of Giving Weekly financial reports, nos. 1-122, incomplete, November 1964-December 1967 (Box 43)
    - Campaign for Michigan (1983-1987), 1983-1985
      - Announcement and volunteer enlistment event, October 14, 1983 (Box 43)
      - Brochures (Box 43)
      - Campaign plan, April 1983 (Box 43)
      - Campaign review meeting with Gerald Ford, January 22, 1983 (Box 43)
      - Chemical Sciences Building Notebook of Commemorative Naming Opportunities (Box 43)
      - Correspondence, 1983 (Box 43)
      - National Leadership Conference, October 29, 1985 (Box 43)
      - Volunteer organization, June 1983 (Box 43)
    - Campaign for Michigan (1990-1997), 1991-1994
      - Brochures, Programs and Invitations (Box 43)
      - The Challenge for the 1990s Transforming the University, 1994 (Box 44)
      - Strategic Plan (Box 44)
      - A Vision for the 21st Century: Beyond "The Leaders and Best" (Box 44)
      - Volunteer meeting, September 13-14, 1991 (Box 44)
      - Volunteer Notebook (Box 44)
    - Campaign planning materials
      - 1980, 4 folders (Box 44)
    - College of Engineering
      - Campaign Completion Program, 1978 (Box 44)
      - Capital Campaign Final Report, 1979 (Box 44)
      - Report of a Study of Fund-Raising Potential and Recommendations, November 1982 (Box 44)
    - Department of Ophthalmology, Report of a Survey of Fund-Raising Potential and Recommendations, October 1979 (Box 44)
    - Enriching a Heritage of Leadership: A Presentation of the Contributions, Potential and Requirements of the University of Michigan, September 1982 (Box 44)
    - Management review and audit, Capital Campaign Office, December 1982 (Box 44)
    - School of Music, Report of a Survey of Fund-Raising Potential and Recommendations, September-October 1981 (Box 44)
  - Committees, 1980-1998
    - Campaign Planning Committee/ Group, 1989
      - Advisory Committee, 1989 (Box 44)
      - Final Report, December 12, 1989 (Box 44)
      - Meeting agendas and materials, 1989
        - January 27, 1989 (Box 44)
        - February 3, 1989 (Box 44)
        - February 10, 1989 (Box 44)
        - February 17, 1989 (Box 44)
        - March 3, 1989 (Box 44)
        - March 10, 1989 (Box 44)
        - March 17, 1989 (Box 44)
        - March 24, 1989 (Box 44)
        - April 7, 1989 (Box 44)
        - April 11, 1989 (Box 44)
        - April 14, 1989 (Box 45)
        - April 21, 1989 (Box 45)
        - April 28, 1989 (Box 45)
        - May 2, 1989 (Box 45)
        - May 5, 1989 (Box 45)
        - May 12, 1989 (Box 45)
        - May 26, 1989 (Box 45)
        - May 26, 1989 (Box 45)
        - June 2, 1989 (Box 45)
        - June 8, 1989 (Box 45)
        - June 11, 1989 (Box 45)
        - June 15, 1989 (Box 45)
        - July 6, 1989 (Box 45)
        - July 13, 1989 (Box 45)
        - July 24, 1989 (Box 45)
        - August 8, 1989 (Box 45)
        - August 31, 1989 (Box 45)
        - October 13, 1989 (Box 45)
        - November 7, 1989 (Box 45)
      - Membership lists, 1989 (Box 45)
      - Sub-committee on Key Assumptions,1989 (Box 45)
    - Campaign Steering Committee, 1990-1993
      - Meeting materials, 1991
        - April 4, 1991 (Box 45)
        - June 7, 1991 (Box 45)
      - Membership lists (Box 45)
      - Memoranda, December 1990-February 1993 (Box 45)
    - Capital Campaign Coordination Committee, 1980
      - Meeting minutes, March 27, 1980-June 11, 1980 (Box 45)
      - Memoranda, February 1980-June 1980 (Box 45)
      - Miscellaneous, 1980 (Box 45)
    - Development Policy Committee, 1981-1984
      - Meeting minutes and materials
        - February 21, 1981-April 23, 1981 (Box 45)
        - April 30, 1981-October 22, 1981 (Box 45)
        - October 29, 1981-December 3, 1981 (Box 45)
        - January 7, 1982-March 4, 1982 (Box 45)
        - March 25, 1982-May 6, 1982 (Box 45)
        - June 3, 1982-July 22, 1982 (Box 45)
        - September 8, 1982-December 23, 1982 (Box 45)
        - January 6, 1983-March 4, 1983 (Box 45)
        - March 14, 1983-April 7, 1983 (Box 45)
        - April 21, 1983-April 28, 1983 (Box 45)
        - May 5, 1983-May 27, 1983 (Box 45)
        - June 6, 1983-July 21, 1983 (Box 46)
        - October 13, 1983-November 3, 1983 (Box 46)
        - January 12, 1984-March 1, 1984 (Box 46)
        - March 22, 1984-June 25, 1984 (Box 46)
        - July 10, 1984-September 11, 1984 (Box 46)
    - Long-Range Planning Committee, 1986-1987
      - Meeting materials and memoranda, October 1986-February 1987 (Box 46)
      - Preliminary Review and Recommendations, May 8, 1987 (Box 46)
      - Report and Recommendations, July 29, 1987 (Box 46)
    - Operations Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 46)
    - Presidential Societies Executive Committee, 1988-1989
      - Correspondence, 1989 (Box 46)
      - Meeting materials, May 20, 1989 (Box 46)
      - Membership lists, 1988-1989 (Box 46)
    - Presidents Advisory Group, 1989-1998
      - Correspondence and memoranda, 1994-1998 (Box 46)
      - Meetings
        - June 1989
          - Attendance lists (Box 46)
          - Correspondence and memoranda, February 1989-July 1989
            - Meeting agendas, notes, and materials (Box 46)
        - November 1989
          - Attendance lists (Box 46)
          - Correspondence and memoranda, August 1989-November1989 (Box 46)
          - Meeting agendas, notes, and materials (Box 46)
        - June 1990
          - Attendance lists (Box 46)
          - Correspondence and memoranda, February 1990-June 1990 (Box 46)
          - Meeting agendas, notes, and materials (Box 46)
        - November 1990
          - Attendance lists (Box 46)
          - Correspondence and memoranda, December 1990-May 1991 (Box 46)
          - Meeting agendas, notes, and materials (Box 46)
        - June 1991
          - Attendance Lists (Box 47)
          - Correspondence and memoranda, December 1990-May 1991 (Box 47)
          - Meeting agendas, notes, and materials (Box 47)
        - December 1991
          - Attendance lists (Box 47)
          - Correspondence and memoranda, February 1991-December 1991 (Box 47)
          - Meeting agendas, notes, and materials (Box 47)
        - June 1992
          - Attendance lists (Box 47)
          - Correspondence and memoranda, June 1992 (Box 47)
          - Meeting agendas, notes, and materials (Box 47)
        - December 1992
          - Attendance lists (Box 47)
          - Correspondence and memoranda, August 1992-December 1992 (Box 47)
          - Meeting agendas, notes, and materials (Box 47)
        - June 1993
          - Attendance lists (Box 47)
          - Correspondence and memoranda, December 1992-June 1993 (Box 47)
          - Meeting agendas, notes, and materials (Box 47)
        - June 1994
          - Attendance lists (Box 47)
          - Correspondence and memoranda, January 1994-May 1994
            - Meeting agendas, notes, and materials (Box 47)
        - December 1994
          - Attendance lists (Box 47)
          - Meeting agendas, notes, and materials (Box 47)
        - September 1995
          - Attendance list (Box 47)
        - June 1996
          - Meeting agenda (Box 47)
        - Members and term assignments, 1994-1998 (Box 47)
  - Topical Files, 1960-1997
    - 1960-1997
      - Annual Report of Voluntary Support, Fiscal Year, 1986 (Box 47)
      - The Challenge of Leadership: A Mission for the 21st Century Presentation, April 1988 (Box 47)
      - Development Council reports and materials, 1969 (Box 47)
      - Development Handbook, 1972 (Box 47)
      - Development Study, John Grezenbach and Associates, materials and correspondence, 1979 (Box 47)
      - Events (agendas and invitations), 1984-1989 (Box 47)
      - Four-year voluntary support projection, July 1981 (Box 47)
      - Gifts, Grants and Contracts, reports and guidelines, 1986 (Box 47)
      - The Michigan Mandate: A Strategic Linking of Excellence and Diversity presentation, November 1988 (Box 47)
      - National Peer Screening Program, 1989 (Box 47)
      - Operation Michigan: Report of the University of Michigan Regents from the Director of University Relations, January-June 1964 (Box 47)
      - Partners in Leadership
        - Photographs (Box 49)
        - Preliminary report, March 5, 1990 (Box 47)
        - Volunteer packet
          - 1989-1990 (Box 47)
          - 1990-1991 (Box 47)
          - 1991-1992 (Box 47)
          - (recognition paperweight and volunteer pin removed to Box 49), 1992-1993 (Box 47)
      - Power, Eugene, trip to International Congress of Orientalists, Moscow, USSR, August 9-16, 1960 (Box 47)
      - Planning for the University of Michigan in the 21st Century presentation, June 1989 (Box 47)
      - Private Giving, Fiscal Year Totals: 1980-1997 and Campaign for Michigan: 1990-1997 (Box 47)
      - Projections--Revenue/ Expense/ Gifts for, 1981-1989 (Box 48)
      - Raoul Wallenberg Medal and Lecture, 1987-1990 (Box 48)
      - Report on Increasing Women's Participation as Volunteers and Donors at the University of Michigan, January 1994 (Box 48)
      - University Relations in the 1980s A Planning Document, February 1992 (Box 48)
  - Debra Griffith Staff Files
    The Debra Griffth Staff Files series contains records created between 19892002. When Griffith began her position as Regional Director of the Major and Planned Gifts Office in the late 1990's, she requested that each academic unit send her their latest fundraising and recruiting information. These files offer a glimpse of the recruitment efforts and of the fundraising goals and initiatives of the different departments of the university between 1989-2002. The varied promotional materials display the unique look and feel of the many departments within the university. It is interesting to note the different strategies that each department employs to attract potential students, especially such news schools at the time as the School of Information. Within this collection there is also fundraising information pertaining to smaller university organizations such as the Center for the Education of Women, Department of Otolaryngology, Institute of Human Adjustment. There is also information relating to the fundraising efforts of Nichols Arboretum and the University of Michigan's Art Museum. The files are arranged alphabetically according to unit title.
    - Arts of Citizenship, 2002 (Box 50)
    - Athletic Department, 2000-2001 (Box 50)
    - Business School, 2001-2002 (Box 50)
    - Cancer Center, 2001-2002 (Box 50)
    - Center for Community Service and Learning, 1999 (Box 50)
    - Center for Education of Women (Box 50)
    - College of Literature, Science, and the Arts, 1999-2002 (Box 50)
    - College of Pharmacy, 2001-2002 (Box 50)
    - Department of Otolaryngology, 1999-2002 (Box 50)
    - Division of Kinesiology, 2001-2002 (Box 50)
    - Hill Auditorium, 2001 (Box 50)
    - Institute for Human Adjustment, 2001 (Box 50)
    - Institute for Social Research, 1999-2000 (Box 50)
    - Law School, 2001 (Box 50)
    - Medical School, 1999 (Box 50)
    - Mott Children's Hospital, 1999-2002 (Box 50)
    - Museum of Art, 1999-2000 (Box 50)
    - Nichols Arboretum, 1999 (Box 50)
    - Gerald R. Ford School of Public Policy, 2000-2001 (Box 50)
    - Rackham Graduate School, 1999 (Box 50)
    - School of Art and Design, 2000-2002 (Box 50)
    - School of Education, 2001-2002 (Box 50)
    - School of Information, 2000 (Box 50)
    - School of Music, 1995-2001 (Box 50)
    - School of Natural Resources and Environment, 2001 (Box 50)
    - School of Nursing, 1999-2000 (Box 50)
    - School of Public Health, 1999 (Box 50)
    - School of Social Work, 1999-2001 (Box 50)
    - University Library, 2001 (Box 50)
    - Women's Health Program, 1997-1999 (Box 50)
  - Development Education Program
    The Development Education Program series contains records created between 1985-2004. It has a wide range of materials relating to the training of university fundraising volunteers and donor relations. The majority of the material within this series falls into three sub-series: Committee Materials, Manuals, and Topical. Within the Committee Materials is documentation relating to the Development Office's Advisory Committee, Matching Gift Advisory Committee and Staff Development Advisory Committee. The larger sub-series contains fundraising manuals that focus on introducing fundraising staff and volunteers to the activities and responsibilities of the development office. They cover such subjects as matching gifts, planned giving, and the development offices' database system named RAMIS. These manuals provide a step by step guide to how the development office trained their staff and what expectations and responsibilities they placed upon them. The topical sub-series contains documents that discuss the history of philanthropy at the university and the university's broad fundraising goals between 1986-2004. There are proposals for university-wide Fundraising initiatives, information on the university's endowment, annual giving, and major gifts. Where the Debra Griffith staff files series focus on the fundraising goals of the separate university departments, the materials in the topical series render a representation of the university's broad fundraising, goals.
    - Alumni Census, 1986; 1994 (Box 50)
    - Calendars
      - 1991-1995 (Box 50)
      - 1996-1997 (Box 50)
    - Campaign Kickoff Planning, 1989-1992 (Box 50)
    - Campaign Planning, 1986-1998; 3 folders (Box 50)
    - Committee Materials
      - Advisory Committee, 1990-1995 (Box 50)
      - Advisory Committee, 1996-1997 (Box 50)
      - Matching Gift Advisory Committee, 1996-1997 (Box 50)
      - Staff Development Advisory Committee, 1996-1997 (Box 50)
    - Development Newsletter, 1991-1998; 2 folders (Box 51)
    - Donor Satisfaction Study, 1996-1999 (Box 51)
    - Estimated Expenditures and Statistics, 1990-1996 (Box 51)
    - History, 1986-1991
      - Development/Alumni/Constituent System, 1990 (Box 51)
      - Development Alumni Constituent System (DACS), 1999. (Box 51)
      - Donor Hotline Management Presentation Booklet, 1996 (Box 51)
      - Donor Prospect Tracking System Users Manual, 1991 (Box 51)
      - Donor Relations Manual, 1989 (Box 51)
      - Fundraising Manual-University Wide, 1985 (Box 51)
      - Help Line Training Guide, 1996 (Box 51)
      - Introduction to Development, 1997-1998 (Box 51)
      - Matching Gift Quality Team Manual-Book 1, 1995 (Box 51)
      - Matching Gift Quality Team Manual-Book 2, 1995 (Box 51)
      - Office of Development Overview, 1998 (Box 51)
      - Orientation Notebook, 1986 (Box 51)
      - Orientation Notebook-Planned Giving, 1999 (Box 51)
      - RAMIS Manual, Part 1, 1987 (Box 52)
      - RAMIS Manual, Part 2,1987 (Box 52)
      - Volunteer Notebook, 1991 (Box 52)
      - Volunteer Notebook, 1992 (Box 52)
    - Program Statistics, 1990-1995 (Box 52)
    - Status Activity Reports, 1990-2001; 2 folders (Box 52)
    - Symposium on Campus Planning, 1989 (Box 52)
    - Topical
      - Admission Standards and Concerns, 1981-1987 (Box 52)
      - Annual Giving, 1986-1997; 2 folders (Box 52)
      - Campaign for Michigan Strategic Plan, 1990-1997 (Box 52)
      - Development Alumni/Constituent System (DACS) Proposal, 1990 (Box 52)
      - Endowment, 1992-1994 (Box 52)
      - Engineering Development, 1998 (Box 52)
      - Expanding Pool of Development Field Staff-Final Report, 2001 (Box 52)
      - History of Philanthropy at University, 1960-2004 (Box 52)
      - Individual Giving, 1987-1988 (Box 52)
      - Major Gifts, 1986-1993 (Box 52)
      - Peer Screening Report, 1990-1993 (Box 52)
      - Summary of Fundraising Objectives for University, 1998 (Box 52)
      - Total Quality Management, 1993-1994 (Box 52)
      - Volunteer Evaluation Survey, 1989 (Box 52)
  - Audio-Visual Materials
    The Audio-Visual Materials series includes audio cassette tapes, and BETA, U-Matic, and VHS videotapes. The cassette tapes contain recordings of several speeches given by former President Ford at the university. The BETA, U-Matic, and VHS videotapes are comprised of two main types, recruitment videos and documentation of the Michigan Fundraising Campaign that officially started in 1992. The recruitment videos offer picturesque views of central campus from the mid-1980's to the early 1990's. The Michigan Fundraising Campaign videos document the many presidential advisory meetings that were held by President Duderstat in 1990 when he, and the advisory board members, addressed such concerns as how the university will adjust to the modem technical environment and how they should adjust the mission and fundraising goals of the university. These concerns were focused before the official 1992 kick off of the large fundraising campaign titled "Campaign for Michigan". The videotapes are noteworthy because they clearly show that this campaign marked a new direction for the university, and that the school as a whole was redefining itself There are discussions that focus on adjusting the managing of the school to resemble the management of a business, and how this change will effect the mission, goals, and responsibilities of the university.
    - U-Matic Tapes
      - Ovation - The Campaign for Hill, 1993; U-matic tape, 16 min., also VHS copy (Box 38)
    - Beta Videotapes (Box 53)
      - Campaign for Michigan, Soliciting Special Gifts, A Guide for (Box 53)
      - Volunteers (Box 53)
      - Mid-Campaign, 15:30, 9/21/1994 (Box 53)
      - Michigan Campaign Mike Walleye Video, 9:11, 1994 (Box 53)
    - Audio Cassette Tapes
      - Gerald Ford, Campaign for Michigan, Close, 18:00 (Box 53)
      - Gerald Ford, Chrysler Arena, Michigan League, Alumni Center (Box 53)
      - 10/14/1983 (Box 53)
      - Campaign for Michigan, Special Gifts, Motivational and Training (Box 53)
      - Film, 1987 (Box 53)
      - Campaign for Michigan, Master (Box 53)
      - Campaign for Michigan, Slide/VT Combo, 8:00 (Box 53)
      - Campaign for Michigan, Volunteer Meeting, 10 Minute Version (Box 53)
      - 1991 (Box 53)
      - "Come on Home to Michigan", Academic/Athletic Salute (Box 53)
      - U of M Heritage", S180511986 (Box 53)
    - VHS Videotapes
      - AGP Development Retreat, 6/6/1991 (Box 53)
      - Alumni Satellite TV Broadcast, President's House, 4/9/1989 (Box 53)
      - Alumni Video, 1991 (Box 53)
      - Campaign for the Advancement of Michigania Programs (C.A.M.P.) (Box 53)
      - Capital Campaign Kickoff Compilation, Image Presentations, 18:00,12/23/1992 (Box 53)
      - Center of Champions, 7/31/1989 (Box 53)
      - Cooperative Education Program: An Investment for Tomorrow (Box 53)
      - Today, Michigan Engineering Television Network, 1992 (Box 53)
      - Hail to the Victors, Hail to the Chief. Highlights from the Spring Commencement, 1991 (Box 53)
      - Lurie Carillon Dedication, 10/17/1996 (Box 53)
      - Lyon Video, Michigan Campaign, 5:25, 5/14/1993 (Box 53)
      - "Risky Business", Michigan Business School Campaign Kick-Off, 1992 (Box 53)
      - "Seeding a Championship" (Box 53)
      - Team Michigan Kickoff Campaign for Michigan, 1992 (Box 53)
      - The Michigan MBA Innovation (Box 53)
      - "The Renaissance of the University of Michigan Golf Course" (Box 53)
      - Vital Signs: University of Michigan Medical Center, 8:45, 1989 (Box 53)
      - Academic Program Group, Development Session, Tape 1-2, 5/11/1992 (Box 54)
      - Campaign for Michigan, 1992 (Box 54)
      - Campaign for Michigan, Institutional Message for Television, 3:30,1993 (Box 54)
      - Campaign for Michigan, Message from Mike Wallace (Box 54)
      - Campaign for Michigan, Parallel Production, 11:35, 1981-1987 (Box 54)
      - Campaign for Michigan, Session 111, 2:15, 9/13/1991 (Box 54)
      - Campaign for Michigan, Session V, 9/14/1991 (Box 54)
      - Campaign for Michigan, Session VI, "The Charge of the Volunteers", 10:00, 9/14/1991 (Box 54)
      - Campaign for Michigan, Unedited Copy, I 1:00-noon, 9/13/1991 (Box 54)
      - Come on Home to Michigan", SPN#20135 College of ENG (Box 54)
      - Consider Michigan", Undergraduate Admission, Produced by Alec Friedman (Box 54)
      - Institutional Message: "Arthur Miller Theater", Prepared for the Regional Basketball Telecast, 2:00 (Box 54)
      - Michigan Generation: Traditions and Youth (Dress Rehearsal), 48:15, BMC #950,1994 (Box 54)
      - Michigan Possible (Box 54)
      - Michigan Spirit: Think of the Possibilities, 2003 (Box 54)
      - Mid-Campaign, Ehrlicher Room, 9/23/1994 (Box 54)
      - Mid-Campaign Event with President Duderstat, 48:00, 1994 (Box 54)
      - Mid-Campaign, Kellogg Auditorium, 9/23/1994 (Box 54)
      - Mid-Campaign, Mendelssohn Theater, 9/23/1994 (Box 54)
      - Mid-Campaign, MLB 4, 9/23/1994 (Box 54)
      - Mid-Campaign, Rackham Amphitheater, 9/23/1994 (Box 54)
      - Passion of a Volunteer Leadership Convocation, 9/20/2002 (Box 54)
      - Presidential Advisory Group, 6/1/1990 (Box 54)
      - President's Advisory Group Meeting, Working Lunch, 6/7/1991 (Box 54)
      - President's Advisory Group, Full Team Meeting, Tape 2, 6/7/1991 (Box 54)
      - President's Advisory Group, Master, Tape I of 2, 12/06/1991 (Box 54)
      - President's Advisory Group, Master, Tape 2 of 2, 12/06/1991 (Box 54)
      - President's Advisory Group, Morning, 1992 (Box 54)